Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every
wall that's in our wake!
Go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming end.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up.
way up high always step up if
waves erupt up to the sky never
give up our wishes they will come
together and lead us on for the
future we drift on riding the
waves towards another shore day by
day there are many meetings many
goodbyes underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if waves are
rough, jump through the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on towards our future.
Hands up.
You're saying the gas
didn't affect you at all?
Well,
Vegapunk himself designed these
protective suits and it turns out
Caesar Clown's evil brain just ain't
no match for that guy's genius.
And Caesar knew that, the bastard!
That's why he told the
guys out in the field
that the suits wouldn't do them any good.
Listen to me!
You'll have to run for it!
Your suits won't protect you
and they'll just slow you down!
So fast the world!
That evil SOB got a whole
ton of our friends petrified.
Let's move out! Yeah!
If Caesar's telling the
truth, we can rescue them.
Even though they're paralyzed in the
shells, they're just in a coma-like state.
But still, we've only got 12 hours to find
them before the poison does kill them.
So any gas statue you
find, bust it wide open!
Thank you, sir.
You're a good man letting us come back
onto the island to search for our friends.
I'll never forget you and
what you've done for us.
As soon as I find my
followers and save them,
I promise I'll come
back and turn myself in.
I know you will, because
this is the only exit.
Get moving already. Right.
Never dealt with anything
like this before.
What the hell do we do with them?
Well, they're some kind of pirates, right?
I don't know, but they're creeping me out.
What?
It looks like severed heads.
That's impossible.
Holy crap, you was right.
Those artists.
What the hell?
What?
This is not good.
Flamingo.
Warlord.
he's using the conqueror's
Haki but why you're on our side
because this isn't about you their
ship is gone you're a warlord what
are you doing attacking in the navy
the pirates had to have shipped
out within the last hour or two at
most now tell me where they went how
dare you attack our guys don't do
it you damn fool get control my body
i can understand law but the straw
hats are nothing more than upstarts
Please, don't do it Why would
you bastards let them go?
Tell me where they went.
Please, just let me live.
That's enough!
You messed with my soldiers, now
you're gonna have to deal with me!
You should be able to tell me
which direction those punks went.
After we leave here, I'm thinking
about heading over to Greenbit.
Nope.
I've got no idea.
Joker.
We almost caught them, but they got away.
I doubt base commander Vergo
is gonna be happy with me.
We both know that he's dead
And that means you know
far too much from my taste.
Take this.
This is pointless.
Stop struggling and die with some dignity
Smokey!
I won't stand here and let him kill you.
Stay back!
Smokey, no!
I get you asking about it,
and you're not the only one.
Everybody's worried about the Mini Mary.
Oh, is that right?
You know it.
In fact, you're the eighth person
I've had to explain this to.
I took the Sunny up a channel by
the lab to get back out to the sea.
Then I circled back
around to the dock where
we first landed to retrieve
the Mini-Mary. Oh, yes.
Very fascinating.
So that's how our sweet little lamb
came back to us safe and sound.
Good story.
Nami, what's the next
stop you got charted?
Oh, give me a second here.
I've set the course.
There won't be any stops.
Hmm?
Straight to Dressrosa. Wait!
The Dressrosa?
You know the place? Yes!
As a matter of fact, that is
the exact destination that we,
or rather I, was hoping to reach.
That is your destination as well?
Sure, or I guess so.
Why is the current shifting?
Are we on a slope? Woo-hoo!
Oh, man, we're moving crazy fast.
Look out for reefs while you're up there.
Can anyone explain what's happening here?
We're on a sea hill.
It's not uncommon.
Yes, it is!
The middle needle on
your log post should be
pointing us in the exact
direction of Dressrosa.
But don't steer us straight there.
I want to take a roundabout way.
Here's something I've been wondering.
I saw you talking to someone on
the transponder snail earlier.
Why don't you tell us who it was?
It was Doflamingo.
Doflamingo?
You mean the warlord?
He's the most evil one.
Why talk to him?
The plan's in action, so
there's no backing out.
What plan?
Want to fill us in?
Yeah, let's tell him about the plan.
Gather round, everybody!
You've formed an alliance to
kill one of the four emperors?
You know, this plan is pretty great.
Wait, everyone just
calm down for a minute.
All right, Luffy, can you
explain this alliance to us?
Sure thing.
Our crew is teaming up with
Traffy's pirate crew to do stuff,
so let's all try to get along.
All against this idea? Me! Me! Me!
Do you really think that's going
to make any sort of difference?
You know what happens once
Luffy's made up his mind.
Thank you, Sanji.
I'll give you a word of warning.
Try not to act too surprised
if it turns out there's a bit
of a difference in how you and
Luffy define the term alliance.
You've been warned.
At least the whole kidnapping
thing makes sense now,
considering it's not Luffy's style.
Usually, if he'd brought
this weird sheep on board,
I would have assumed he wanted me to
throw it in a pot and cook it up for him.
Do you simpletons honestly believe that
you're going to get away with this madness?
You're about to have some of the most
powerful names in the world hunting you down.
You pea-brained savages, your
stupidity will be your death.
There's a special place in hell for...
Not cool, Sanji.
I'm still treating him.
Wait till I'm done.
What, and then it's okay?
You guys executed stage
one of the plan when
I asked you to kidnap
Caesar on Punk Hazard.
And while you were doing that,
I destroyed the machine
manufacturing the chemical SAD.
Most of the great pirates in the New
World rule over their own territories,
governed by their subordinates.
They've got a countless
number of followers,
and they reign over all like
an enormous criminal syndicate.
It's nothing like anything any
of you have dealt with before.
Trying to take them down with
a single pirate crew won't
even get you close enough
to see their captain's face.
With that said,
they still have to operate underground
all their deals are carried out in secret;
it's the only way they can
safely avoid naval attention.
And the most trusted among them,
the one with easily the most power
and influence, is Doflamingo.
His underground alias is Joker, and
out of all of Joker's business deals,
he's got one client who's
more important than the rest.
His biggest spender is
one of the four emperors,
Kaido—the king of the
beasts—and there you have it.
That's our target, surely?
You cannot hope to defeat him.
Something wrong?
Oh, don't mind me; by all means, go on!
go on
What is this dragon doing here?
Where did Momonosuke go? That is Momo
Getting back to the point
If we want to defeat
Kaido We have to strike
at his alliances Before
we face him head on
Here's the deal He's getting a
bunch of devil fruits from Joker
A mass produced Snow type called Smile
They can make those So
he can cook up a whole
army of people with Snow
powers if he wants to?
That's the idea.
How are you so calm about this?
It seems the man-made
fruits aren't quite stable.
But even with the risk involved, Kaido's
army now has over 500 power holders.
Who doesn't want to do this?
Raise your hand!
Would you shut up, sir?
Although, at least we stopped
them from producing more fruits.
Really?
He's the one who was making them?
Wow, that's what S .A .D.
does?
They use it to make devil fruits?
Cool!
Very impressive.
Don't praise him! S .A .D.
is that hard to make?
Only he can do it?
It was Vegapunk's discovery.
Caesar just put lineage
factor to practical use.
I knew this guy was crap.
Oh, I'm not a genius!
Then you try making S .A .D.!
You don't even have the sense
to stop running your mouth.
We've stopped the source of production.
Next step is to wipe out the distribution.
There's a factory on Dressrosa that
manufactures and ships the stuff out.
And you're saying we should
go and bust the place up?
He won't just watch his empire crumble.
He has powerful followers, so
we should be ready for a fight.
Dressrosa, huh?
You said you needed to go
there too, right, Keen?
Yes, indeed!
One of my comrades is there!
Held prisoner by our foe!
Please, leave him alone!
We've done his mess, man!
Stop it!
You can't take him from us! Please!
We're nothing but a bunch of misfits!
He's the only one who has faith in us!
We'll be finished!
Oh, don't you worry.
Much as I wish I could,
I can't read minds.
So every last one of you might
know more than you should not
just you same goes for law on the
Straw Hat the whole island, too
So I'll just have to kill you all
Hold on there
Pardon me for the intrusion
I'm afraid I need you to step aside
That man you intend on killing right there
He's an old friend of mine
Whoa, what the hell's Aokiji doing here?
Oh, no!
Young master!
I'm not really looking
to pick a fight with you.
But you should encourage your
friend to keep his trap shut.
You might not like how
things go otherwise.
While we're here, let me
ask you something. Hm?
You're not a marine.
So what the hell are you, Kuzan?
Your reputation's not too good these days.
Are you going to give the
man some first aid or what?
Oh, yes, sir!
There's a difference in the look of a
vagabond and that of a man newly determined.
He's found a purpose.
You can see it in his eyes.
I never thought the world
government was absolute, you know.
There's plenty of things I can accomplish
in this world without
being a navy admiral.
And plenty of things I can see now that I
was blind to before I was as good as dead.
Well maybe it was faith that brought
me here—why'd you really come here?
I came to see you!
you
And how did you know where I'd be?
Ah, damn it.
Don't tell me you're in with
the black market dealers now.
Is that it?
How do you go from the Navy to that?
If you're done patching
them up, then scram!
Smoker, I'm still me. All right?
Then I can trust you.
Anyway, you should keep
an eye on Doflamingo.
He's not just a warlord,
but the king of Dressrosa.
And don't think that makes him
like the snake princess, either.
He's in a class of his own,
as dangerous as they come.
Tell Sakazuki to mobilize
the admirals right away.
Worst case scenario, things
could go wrong very quickly.
This will be the biggest challenge
he's faced as fleet admiral for sure.
Maybe the biggest in his life.
Well, you've been warned.
One last thing—don't
tell anyone you saw me.
If
word gets out then uh.
Who
cares?
Never
mind then later.
later
We've made it to the end of the day.
No enemy sighted anywhere.
Sir, no enemy's found on my patrol either.
Good work. At ease, soldier. Thank you.
Hey, are we safe yet or what?
How many people are looking for us?
Like a whole army?
I'm afraid the second I lay down,
Doflamingo's gonna swoop
in and kill me in my sleep!
He's gonna get all of us killed!
He gave us these cool helmets!
I bet we're, like, invincible now!
Designing from the warlords of the seer,
go into battle with one
of the four emperors.
Obviously, he'll pass on both
and come kill us if he's wise.
Oh, I'm scared.
Stop fleeing and face your
punishment, you spineless coward!
Don't jump to conclusions,
it's complicated. Get away!
Would you stop fighting on the ship?
You're gonna sink us all!
You guys playing Samurai? Fight! Fight!
Have you no shame?
The wanted kingdom heartbroken!
The brave of our hero!
Defiled!
I told you I couldn't take it!
Am I to believe that our hero
Ryuba's legendary blade, Chouchou,
simply fell into your lap?
You're a real pal, Samurai.
Cut them in half for me.
Hey, guys, how's the midnight
snack sound? Awesome!
What's on the menu? Pizza.
Pita?
I am not familiar with this dish by name,
but if your chef made
it, I'm eager to try it.
Did Momonosuke go to bed already?
He's taking a bath with Robin right now.
What?
You haven't had a chance to bathe
in days, have you? Quite true.
Are you all nice and warm now?
Indeed.
Most relaxing.
Oh, perfect timing.
Kin'emon, he needs some
clothes, if you would.
What are you grinning about,
you dirty little brat?
We can see right through
that act of yours.
You think you can get away with
this just because you're a kid?
You must now cut off
your top knot and shame.
Hey, why are you ganging
up on a child, you jerks?
He's a man in his heart.
Do not let him fool you, Nami.
Say I feel the part of the princess.
You think I'm a princess?
Well, I won't disagree.
Aw, you're such a good boy.
You sleep with me and Robin tonight.
No!
Their bedroom is a secret garden.
You don't get to go.
What?!
You're a filthy little devil, I knew it!
I just know Doflamingo's gonna
sneak up on us in the dead of night.
Getting over with already, man?
Better yet, just don't come at all!
We can never fall asleep again!
Looks like the horizon is all clear. Yep.
It's the news.
Look, there's a story about Doflamingo.
It says here.
He resigned!
And he gave up the throne of Dressrosa?
What is that about?
Huh, if he had a throne, then
doesn't that mean he was a king?
Him, really?
Who would that guy rule over?
Birds, I guess.
Ain't to be a downer,
but don't you think this whole thing's
working out to be a little too convenient?
Nah, it's a good thing.
I mean, since he didn't
have a choice in the matter.
Hey, look at that!
There's a picture of
me and Traffy in here!
Trafalgar Law of the Seven Warlords?
Forms an alliance with
the Straw Hat Pirates?
It remains to be seen how the government
will choose to punish Law. Oh dear.
Sure is a lot going on in the world today!
Dove Lamingo quit the Warlords and
now Law's working with the Straw Hats?
And then, to top it all off, Captain
Kidd, Scratchman Apu, Basil Hawkins.
It says the Kidd Pirates,
the Honor Pirates,
and the Hawkins Pirates have
formed an alliance though too.
Man, today's news just
keeps getting crazier.
I wonder why.
Those are the troublemakers we've
been keeping an eye on for two years.
So why are they in
cahoots all of a sudden?
It looks like things are about
to get intense in the new world.
This is huge.
I can't believe all those crews have
decided to join forces like that.
Yeah, just like we did.
I guess we had the right idea, didn't we?
Forget about them.
Let's stick with our original plan.
We'll keep our focus on Doflamingo.
Think about it.
Yesterday's negotiation was more
crucial for him than you realized.
All we did was kidnap Caesar, remember?
And yet practically overnight,
he gave up not only the throne he's
been sitting on for the past 10 years,
but also the government's Carrot
blanche he was given as a privilege.
when he became a warlord.
If he did that just to get Caesar back,
that should tell us a lot about his motives.
Please answer us, your majesty!
It's me—you'll be happy to
know I've resigned. resigned